UTAGE: This makes 900.
UTAGE: I just need 100 more
to secure Tamon-kun's victory.
UTAGE: Work's calling me?
SIGN: Cleaning Made Easy
UTAGE: Hello, this is Kinoshita.
CLEANING MADE EASY PRESIDENT: Oh, Kinoshita-san?
CLEANING MADE EASY PRESIDENT: I know this is sudden,
but are you free tomorrow afternoon?
UTAGE: Yes! I will take on all the work
to financially support Tamon-kun!
CLEANING MADE EASY PRESIDENT: Well, that's good.
CLEANING MADE EASY PRESIDENT: Someone personally asked
for you, so good luck.
UTAGE: Huh? Someone asked for me?
UTAGE: Who, though?
OURI: You're here.
UTAGE: Wha—
UTAGE: Ouri Sakaguchi AKA Gorilla!
OURI: If I become the center, come over to me!
UTAGE: I accept.
UTAGE: What do you want?
The winner hasn't been decided yet.
OURI: What's with that attitude?
OURI: I'm the customer here.
OURI: This is a separate matter.
UTAGE: H-Hey!
UTAGE: By the way...
UTAGE: Is this place your...
OURI: This is my parents' place.
OURI: I'm not made to live in such a cramped
and filthy apartment like that.
OURI: More importantly...
OURI: Are you going out with him?
UTAGE: Huh? With whom?
OURI: Tamon.
UTAGE: Me? Go out with Tamon-kun?
UTAGE: I wuv you.
TAMON: I know.
UTAGE: What?!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun would never settle for one girl.
UTAGE: He's someone who's eventually going to
make all of humanity his girlfriends.
UTAGE: Disparage him again, and I'll turn you
into dust for your sacrilege.
OURI: Knock it off with that weird aura.
OURI: If you're not, it's fine.
That's all I wanted to know.
OURI: Now, leave.
UTAGE: You called me all the way here
to ask me that?!
UTAGE: Please don't waste our time... Huh?
UTAGE: Hey, wait! Huh?
UTAGE: Sakaguchi-san?!
LYRICS: Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
LYRICS: Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
LYRICS: Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
LYRICS: Smooth as ever, I escort you
LYRICS: And this voice, seducing you
LYRICS: Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
LYRICS: I am your ace darlin'
LYRICS: Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
LYRICS: Please Please
LYRICS: Whisper just to me, call my name
LYRICS: You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
LYRICS: But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
LYRICS: Hey, girl
LYRICS: Look this way!
LYRICS: I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
LYRICS: Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
LYRICS: Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
LYRICS: I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
LYRICS: And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
LYRICS: So take my hand and let's roll
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
LYRICS: It's a spell that makes your heart race
LYRICS: We can't go back
LYRICS: You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
OURI: It's hot... That's cold!
UTAGE: Are you awake?
OURI: Wh-What are you doing here?!
OURI: Also, don't just put a cooling pad on me!
You don't know me like that!
UTAGE: Two of the five of the rounds
to determine the center have ended
UTAGE: and Tamon-kun and Ouri-kun
are currently tied for first place.
SIGN: 1st
SIGN: 5th
SIGN: 3rd
SIGN: 1st
SIGN: 4th
UTAGE: No one knows how
it's going to end just yet.
UTAGE: And currently...
OURI: I told you to leave!
UTAGE: A nursing event activated.
UTAGE: And it's not even with my oshi.
UTAGE: How could I leave when
you literally collapsed right on me?
UTAGE: When were talking earlier,
UTAGE: you thought that Gloomyhara-san
and I were in a special relationship,
UTAGE: and you summoned me here
to find out the truth.
OURI: What else was I supposed to do?
OURI: I had no other way of contacting you.
UTAGE: Well, no matter the reason,
UTAGE: I did all I could in the allotted time
since I came here for work.
OURI: Wha—But why?
OURI: I thought you hated me.
UTAGE: This is my job.
OURI: Hey...
OURI: Come back tomorrow.
UTAGE: Please make your appointments
over the phone.
UTAGE: Well, please take care.
UTAGE: I'm exhausted since his house was so big.
UTAGE: Next, I have to go
to Gloomyhara-san's place...
UTAGE: Am I nervous?
UTAGE: I haven't seen Gloomyhara-san
since the summer festival.
UTAGE: I saw various sides of him
that I'd never seen before...
UTAGE: so I...
GLOOMYHARA: Uta-chan.
UTAGE: Hngh!
UTAGE: I'm sure that was just
Hottiehara-san peeking through!
TAMON: Kill me now.
UTAGE: Thank goodness
it's just business as usual.
TAMON: Kinoshita-san...
Did you go to Ouri-kun's place?
UTAGE: H-How did you know?
TAMON: Ouri-kun told me.
SIGN: Me
SIGN: She came over.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Look.
UTAGE: Why would he tell Tamon-kun that?
UTAGE: He's asked me to come by again tomorrow,
UTAGE: so I'll go by and take care of him...
TAMON: Is Ouri-kun sick?!
UTAGE: Huh? You didn't know?
TAMON: He didn't come to rehearsals today.
TAMON: He just said he was taking the day off.
TAMON: Did he just not want us
to know he was weakened?
UTAGE: He's like some wild animal.
TAMON: Is he all right?
UTAGE: His parents were apparently abroad,
so they weren't home,
UTAGE: but I'll go see how he's doing
again tomorrow.
UTAGE: You just focus on yourself,
Gloomyhara-san.
TAMON: Right.
UTAGE: Your fever's gone up since yesterday.
OURI: It has not!
UTAGE: It has.
OURI: Nuh-uh!
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san was worried about you.
OURI: Don't talk about him.
UTAGE: Just like Tamon-kun,
UTAGE: I bet Ouri-kun's under a lot of pressure
during this competition for the center.
UTAGE: Can those two just not get along?
UTAGE: Huh?
TAMON: Pardon me.
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san?!
OURI: What the hell are you doing here?!
TAMON: I came to see how you're doing.
SIGN: White Sugar
TAMON: I know you like sweet things,
but I didn't know exactly what.
OURI: I don't want any!
That's not even funny! Leave!
SIGN: White Sugar
TAMON: Oh, okay. I'll return to the earth now.
UTAGE: Please stop!
UTAGE: He was just scared you'd yell at him
for picking the wrong thing.
OURI: So annoying!
OURI: Usually, you'd avoid me like
the plague, so what gives?
TAMON: Well, you've never had to skip rehearsals
because you were sick before,
TAMON: so I got worried...
OURI: Oho? So you came here because
you were concerned about me?
OURI: If that's true, then put yourself to work.
OURI: Hmph. For my sake.
UTAGE: I've been to bigger homes
for work a number of times,
UTAGE: but this is the first one with a pool.
TAMON: This is my first time coming over,
so I'm also surprised.
UTAGE: Um...
UTAGE: How exactly do you feel about
Sakaguchi-san, Gloomyhara-san?
TAMON: He scares me.
TAMON: Ouri-kun hates me.
TAMON: But... I can't blame him.
TAMON: When I came out to Tokyo to audition
and was basically a lost, little puppy,
TAMON: Ouri-kun was the one who
taught me all kinds of things.
SIGN: Audition\hVenue
OURI: Today's venue is over there.
TAMON: Th-Thank you very much.
OURI: You can be my minion.
OURI: Ask me anything.
TAMON: Okay!
TAMON: And yet...
MC: In first place is...
MC: Tamon Fukuhara!
TAMON: Huh?
TAMON: I figured I couldn't hold anything
he said to me against him.
TAMON: I'd even be willing to give up
the center spot to him.
TAMON: But lately, something's different.
TAMON: I've been feeling like there
must be some other way...
TAMON: That's what I thought when I heard
that Ouri-kun wasn't feeling well.
TAMON: I don't like having to compete
with Ouri-kun when he's not at his best.
TAMON: I think I sort of understand
why Ouri-kun's so irritated with me.
TAMON: So this time...
TAMON: I'm not holding back.
TAMON: An... angel?
TAMON: Whoa!
OURI: Quit your useless yappin' and get to work!
TAMON: Ouri-kun.
TAMON: Please get over your cold
as soon as possible.
TAMON: Because I'll defeat you
with everything I have.
OURI: That's some big talk.
OURI: This time, I'll make sure I crush you
so hard that there'll be nothing left.
OURI: Go out in a blaze of glory.
TAMON: I-I'm not going out!
OURI: What? Who do you think you are, huh?!
TAMON: Um, I am older than you, you know...
OURI: You got a problem?
TAMON: You should be in bed.
SIGN: Uta
OURI: Shut up! Don't tell me what to do!
TAMON: That's cold!
OURI: Hey! Come back here, you dumb minion!
TAMON: I'm not your minion...
OURI: What? I made you one when we first met.
TAMON: P-Please don't spray me with water.
OURI: I'll just keep doing it!
SIGN: Utage Kinoshita
UTAGE: And so, their battle continued...
SIGN: Quiz
SIGN: Battle
MC: Round 3 in our competition
to determine the center...
MC: The winner is Ouri Sakaguchi!
OURI: I did it!
MC: Round 4 is a hidden talent battle!
TAMON: I went into this imagining that each
and every glass was one of my fans.
TAMON: I protected all of you.
MC: The winner is Tamon Fukuhara!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is currently in first place.
SIGN: 5th
SIGN: 4th
SIGN: 3rd
SIGN: 2nd
SIGN: 1st
SIGN: 3rd
SIGN: 2nd
SIGN: 1st
UTAGE: And the fans' support
got even more fired up
UTAGE: as the rankings kept changing
at a dizzying pace.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Yoshiko Harahara @hara2yoshiko
My oshi is perfect in whatever he does!!
#FofF #TamonFukuharaSupportGroup
Tamon Believer @tamonhagod333
Hoooooooly issh (Dead)
#TamonFukuharaSupportGroup #FofF
SIGN: Tamon Superiority Girl @girl_tamon_017
The day draws near where Tamon-kun will cause
all of his girlfriends to overdose on Tamon
and the world will be filled with Tamon-kun
#FofF
megu @megu_star2000
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, oh shit, he's just so beautiful!!
#FofF #TamonFukuharaSupportGroup
UTAGE: Meanwhile...
RIKO: Okay, here we go!
UTAGE: For some reason, we had
perfectly copied Tamon-kun's dance
UTAGE: and shot a dance cover video.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Amon-tay
SIGN: Cheering on Tamon-kun by perfectly
covering his dance
#F/ACE #Tamon-kunIsAGod #FACEOFF
#TriedDancingLikeTamon-kun
#TamonFukuharaSupportGroup #FofF
SIGN: Trending
SIGN: Recommendations
SIGN: Comments
SIGN: Live
SIGN: Settings
SIGN: My Page
SIGN: Tamon
UTAGE: The final battle is going to
be a singing battle.
UTAGE: It'll all come down to their abilities.
SIGN: First appearance!
RANDO GIRL 1: Ah, it's F/ACE!
RANDO GIRL 2: I wonder who's going
to win center.
RANDO GIRL 1: It's gotta be Tamon-kun.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: F/ACE's Battle for the Center
SIGN: Starting at 3:30PM Saturday
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: N Station Summer Fes Begins!!
ANNOUNCER: There's news regarding the popular group F/ACE,
ANNOUNCER: as the final results of
their competition for center
ANNOUNCER: will be announced live at the
N Station Summer Fes venue.
TAMON: Thank you again for today.
UTAGE: It was nothing. Please excuse me.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun looks so relieved
after talking to Ouri-kun.
UTAGE: I'm so glad that he seems
to be in good spirits.
TAMON: Huh?
TAMON: I guess she forgot this.
SIGN: Tamon-kun
OURI: Thanks for the other day, I guess.
UTAGE: Don't worry about it.
It looks like you're feeling better now.
OURI: Of course, I am!
You saw the third round, didn't you?
OURI: And how brilliantly I won!
UTAGE: Well, Tamon-kun won the fourth round.
OURI: So what?
OURI: The last competition is a singing one.
OURI: I'm gonna leave everyone else
in my dust and win!
UTAGE: But...
TAMON: I don't like having to compete
with Ouri-kun when he's not at his best.
UTAGE: Please...
UTAGE: do your best until the very end.
SIGN: Tamon-kun
OURI: You...
UTAGE: I'm sure that Tamon-kun will be happy
if Ouri-kun is able to do his best.
UTAGE: Please be careful not to
catch a cold again.
OURI: I'll take back our agreement from before.
UTAGE: Huh?
OURI: But...
OURI: If I win, be my fan.
SIGN: Tamon
UTAGE: Then...
SIGN: We all belong to the Church of Tamon
UTAGE: If Tamon-kun wins, please become his fan!
OURI: I don't need this crap!
OURI: Take that!
UTAGE: How dare you?!
OURI: Hey!
TAMON: RAIN—rain is falling
FUJITA: You're still here?
TAMON: I'm sorry. I just wanted to
practice a little longer.
FUJITA: You sure are working hard,
but don't overdo it.
TAMON: Yes, sir.
UTAGE: He's asleep.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Mostly lives in a corner
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san, who lives his life
always cowering over something,
UTAGE: is asleep in front of someone
completely unguarded? What in the world?!
UTAGE: But you know...
UTAGE: After taking a break on his eyelashes,
UTAGE: you could probably use
his cheeks as a slide.
UTAGE: We live in the same dimension,
so how is this one person so high-res?!
UTAGE: Everyone who lines up next to Tamon-kun
is basically reduced to pixel art!
UTAGE: In a different world, he might've been
sentenced to death from beauty harassment!
UTAGE: I wonder if this is what it'd be like if
Cleopatra reincarnated as a hot guy.
UTAGE: But... his face seems
paler than usual somehow.
UTAGE: Hm?
UTAGE: Don't push yourself too hard.
UTAGE: Please do your best until the very end.
UTAGE: There is definitely something
resting on my back right now.
UTAGE: There's no way that
it's Tamon-kun, is there?
UTAGE: "Things like that only
happen in your dreams."
UTAGE: That's what Imaginary Gramma
always used to say.
UTAGE: Wait. Did I fantasize so much that I'm not
just seeing them, but also feeling them?
UTAGE: Because I got too excited
seeing my oshi asleep? Oh, shit.
UTAGE: Wait. Tamon-kun's working so hard!
This isn't the time to be fantasizing!
UTAGE: Utage, you need to get to work!
UTAGE: Tomorrow's finally the last battle.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: N Station Summer Fes
8/15
SIGN: Tickets Secured
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Accept
SIGN: Go Back
SIGN: Tamon
UTAGE: Everything will be decided soon.
UTAGE: Please...
SIGN: Tamon
UTAGE: Let Tamon-kun be rewarded
for all his hard work.
NATSUKI: Aw man...
NATSUKI: I totally would've had a chance
NATSUKI: if we didn't have that
weird physical competition.
SIGN: Currently in 4th Place
Natsuki Ishibashi
NATSUKI: Could we not do something so outdated?
KEITO: Quit moping about it.
SIGN: Currently in 5th
Rintaro Kai
KEITO: They said there'd be bonus points
depending on how we ranked
KEITO: in today's competition, remember?
SIGN: Currently in 2nd
Keito Tachibana
KEITO: There's still a chance
you can turn this around.
NATSUKI: Must be nice to be
so calm in second place.
KEITO: I wouldn't say I'm calm at all.
KEITO: Oh?
KEITO: Good morning, Tamon.
NATSUKI: What's up? It's rare for you to be late.
TAMON: Good... morning...
THREE: Huh?
KEITO: Your voice is all raspy! What happened?!
KEITO: Oh, Ouri.
KEITO: Morning.
OURI: Good morning...
FOUR: Huh?!
SHIRAISHI: You'll all be singing
the new song "RAIN" in full today.
SHIRAISHI: I'm sure you've all
practiced your hearts out.
SHIRAISHI: Make sure you give it your all
so you won't have any regrets.
UTAGE/RIKO/YUINA: You've got this, Tamon-kun!
SHIRAISHI: Let the final battle
to determine the center begin!
SIGN: Singing Expert
YUINA: Way to go, Tamon-kun! He definitely
secured the center with that!
RIKO: Unlike the first round,
it actually sounded
RIKO: like he was singing a ballad
about heartbreak, didn't it?!
YUINA: Yeah! He did his best and was shining!
UTAGE: It actually seemed like he was
holding back his radiance...
UTAGE: but it also seemed like
he wasn't doing that well.
RIKO: He's never sung like that before, has he?
YUINA: We saw another new side of Tamon!
RIKO: Right?
UTAGE: No! As Tamon-kun's fan,
I need to believe in him!
SHIRAISHI: All five episodes have
concluded without issue.
SHIRAISHI: The results are as I just told you.
SHIRAISHI: The new song's pre-release at N Station's
Summer Fes is just around the corner.
SHIRAISHI: I need you all to start practicing
SHIRAISHI: the parts you've been assigned immediately.
SHIRAISHI: Also...
SHIRAISHI: Ouri, Tamon!
SHIRAISHI: What was that miserable display?!
SHIRAISHI: You might've fooled the viewers,
SHIRAISHI: but you can't deceive me or the judges!
SHIRAISHI: Are you really the same two that competed
for first and second at the audition?
SHIRAISHI: Practicing too much and overwork
are both signs of failure!
SHIRAISHI: To become the best in the world,
SHIRAISHI: you need to perform
at 2, 000% at any time!
SHIRAISHI: F/ACE doesn't need any imperfections!
YUINA: There's so much fan merch!
RIKO: I'm gonna get this pink one.
SIGN: Victory
YUINA: Hey look at this one.
Obviously a must-buy.
UTAGE: Hm...
UTAGE: The more I rewatch it, the more
it looks like he wasn't doing very well.
UTAGE: What am I going to do if Tamon-kun
doesn't become the center?
UTAGE: I wonder how Gloomyhara-san's
feeling right about now...
UTAGE: I hope he's not all depressed from
doomscrolling for his name.
UTAGE: Have you been eating something
other than cup noodles?
UTAGE: Have you been sleeping in your bed?
RIKO: Let's make a banner, too!
YUINA: We were allowed to bring those in, right?
RIKO: Yeah, we can this time!
YUINA: Heck yeah! Now, then...
UTAGE: You're not obsessing...
and crying again, are you?
UTAGE: I never worried like this
before meeting Gloomyhara-san...
UTAGE: Am I... a failure as a fan?
OURI: You usually just practice
exactly as you're told to
OURI: without saying anything
about how you feel...
OURI: Yet you choose now to
act up and self-destruct?
OURI: How stupid are you?
TAMON: Yeah, but... you didn't do
well this time either, Ouri-kun.
OURI: Shut up! I always sorta choke
when it counts!
OURI: I tried too hard and basically imploded.
OURI: Meaning, it's all your fault.
TAMON: What?
OURI: And what happened to you?
TAMON: There are even more people
supporting me now...
TAMON: and that made me happy.
TAMON: At the same time, I got
overwhelmed with the feelings
TAMON: of absolutely not wanting
to fail or betray them.
TAMON: It's weird.
TAMON: The more they're nice to me,
the more happy and scared I become.
TAMON: I start to wonder what I'll do
if I ever lose them...
TAMON: and then I get scared again.
OURI: Gross.
OURI: There are going to be
some fans who drift away.
OURI: And there'll be some fans who won't.
OURI: There's no point in thinking
about something so obvious.
OURI: I just don't get it.
TAMON: I thought I understood that in my head...
TAMON: But maybe I just thought I understood.
TAMON: All those kind words and yet...
TAMON: What the heck am I even doing?
OURI: How long are you gonna dwell
on what happened in the past?
SIGN: Tamon FTW
Credits: \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation Check:
Credits: Michelle Tymon
\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza\h
Alicia Ashby\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan
RIKO: Wow, I think most of the
people here are here for F/ACE.
YUINA: I'm starting to get nervous!
UTAGE: We're finally going to learn the results.
MC: Thank you all for waiting!
MC: The competition to decide the center
has finally reached its conclusion!
MC: We'll find out which member is the center
with today's performance!
RIKO/YUINA: Tamon-kun! You've got this!
UTAGE: He always sparkles onstage
and presents us with a dream...
UTAGE: I love that Tamon-kun
lets us escape reality.
UTAGE: But behind that,
exists a very real Tamon-kun...
MC: This is F/ACE with "RAIN."
KEITO FANS: You did it, Keito!
OURI FANS: Why, though?!
UTAGE: The one who stresses out,
gets depressed, fails...
UTAGE: And cries his eyes out a lot...
RIKO: Tamon-kun didn't make it...
YUINA: No way... This can't be real...
UTAGE: Even then, he didn't run away in the end.
UTAGE: And now that I know that about him...
SIGN: Tamon-kun will
always be the center in my heart
UTAGE: I just can't help but be
even more devoted to him.
SIGN: Tamon-kun will always be the center in my heart
SIGN: Tamon-kun will
always be the center in my heart
SIGN: Ouri Love
SIGN: Tamon Love
SONG: With raindrops soaking my shoulders
SONG: I even forgot that I'd forgotten
my umbrella somewhere
SONG: Ah, the brightness shines
on my emptiness
SONG: Loneliness melts away my resentment
SONG: That day I met you
SONG: And the day we both got
drenched in the rain
SONG: The rain I knew—
SONG: Was it always
SONG: This cold?
SONG: I realize it only now
SONG: RAIN starts falling
SONG: Washing everything away
SONG: Why couldn't I realize it back then?
SONG: The sky in a morning without you—
so carelessly clear
SONG: The RAIN won't stop
SONG: Under the sky, I start running
SONG: It's a new start - My days with you
SONG: I tuck them into my heart
and now I take a new step forward
SONG: Thank you for being there
SONG: RAIN—rain is falling